nosubhealth.com 2011-02-26

# Privacy Policy | No Sub Health | How to get better health.

Your privacy on the Internet is of utmost importance to the No-Subhealth. This privacy statement describes No-Subhealth’s policy concerning the gathering and sharing of visitors’ information through the No Subhealth web site. It applies to all ” No Subhealth sites” — that is, all sites within the ” NoSubhealth.com” domain name.

**What information does No-Subhealth collect?**

Normal web site usage: In general, you can browse the No-Subhealth site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The only information we gather during general browsing is from standard server logs. These include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system, and information such as the web site that referred you to us, the files you download, the pages you visit, and the dates/times of those visits.

**Collection of personally identifiable information**

If you register for a newsletter, log on to certain No-Subhealth sites, request information, provide feedback, join a discussion group or join an electronic mailing list, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, postal address and e-mail address. This information is collected only with your knowledge and permission, and is kept in various No-Subhealth databases. No-Subhealth sites with specific requirements to collect personal information may publish a privacy policy specific for that site. In these cases, the site-specific policies will be complementary to this general No-Subhealth privacy policy, but will give additional details for that particular site. Joining electronic discussion groups may mean that other participants of the discussion group (including non- No-Subhealth employees) will see personal information that you have volunteered. For open discussion groups, this information will be public.

**What does No-Subhealth do with the information it collects?**

Normal web site usage: The information gathered during general browsing of the ” NoSubhealth.com” domain is used to analyze trends and usage of the No-Subhealth site and to improve the usefulness of the site. It is not connected with any personal information.

**Personally identifiable information**

No-Subhealth may use the personal information you provide to: Contact you — either in response to a query or suggestion, or to mail newsletters, documents, publications etc. to you; “Remember” your online profile and preferences; Help you quickly find information that is relevant to you based on your interests, and help us create site content most relevant to you.

**What if I don’t want to provide personal information?**

Providing personal information on the No-Subhealth site is optional. If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still browse and use the No-Subhealth site.

**Security**

We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the No-Subhealth site to any third party. Any information provided to No-Subhealth by users of the No-Subhealth site is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways other than as set forth in this privacy policy, or in any site-specific policies, or in ways to which you have explicitly consented. No-Subhealth employs a range of technologies and security measures to protect the information maintained on our systems from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. All our employees who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of official business matters, including personal data.

The No-Subhealth site contains links to sites external to the NoSubhealth.com domain. No-Subhealth is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
